mastersoftrivia.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy Policy - Masters of Trivia

* * *

**"No one should compel himself to show to others more of his inner life than he feels it natural to show"**  
(ALBERT SCHWEITZER, 1875-1965; Memoirs of Childhood and Youth, 1925)

We at Masters of Trivia ("MOT") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

MOT has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information includes any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit MOT's web pages and download and use MOT's software applications without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

If you do choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, or by email communications with us, we may transfer that Information, within MOT or to MOT's third party service providers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world including, specifically, the Republic of Panama as necessary. Wherever your Personal Information may be held within MOT or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

Our web pages do not use cookies but our web servers do utilize IP address tracking technologies. These tracking technologies are standard web server log files that may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of these tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics. If you chose to have a relationship with MOT, such as a contractual or other business relationship, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.

MOT does not intend to transfer any Personal Information to third parties who are not bound to act on MOT's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Nevertheless, Personal Information may be transferred in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business of MOT and/or its subsidiaries.

MOT's web site is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect any information at all from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have personal information concerning a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

We are committed to privacy. Protecting your privacy on-line is an evolving area, and MOT's web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@mastersoftrivia.com](mailto:privacy@mastersoftrivia.com). While we cannot and do not guarantee perfect privacy, we will strive to address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time. 

If you found a typo please select the text and press Ctrl + Enter
